

Mobile Hybrid Application
Website Developer
web 3.0 && blockchain

PROFILE

I am a Web & Mobile Technology Enthusiast, with 5+ years of work experience combined with many years of development experience dating back to my college days. I love learning new technologies and staying up to date. And I incorporate these new methods in project development, improving my skills and simultaneously adding value to the organization. I am passionate about what I do and feel happy when we deliver a quality product in efficient ways.

Together We Win.

CONTACT

- **977-348-2697**
- aleharish
- aleharishhp@gmail.com
- www.harishale.com

EXPERIENCE

IBM

2020-2022 - SENIOR SYSTEM ENGINEER

Working as a Frontend Engineer in a cloud-based Salesforce project mainly in AngularJS, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, SLDS, LWC. Integrated a Smart Contract using Blockchain technology for confidential data. Completing CRs, SRs and Product Launch.

Bristlecone India Pvt. Ltd.

2018-2020 - TECHNICAL CONSTULTANT

I worked here as a Hybrid App Developer to build Android and iOS applications using ionic Framework and also build websites using Angular. Core team member of the MESOP project which is an ESOP platform for the Mahindira Group.

Fuelfortech Pvt. Ltd.

2017-2018 - WEB / APP / BACKEND - DEVELOPER

Worked as a Full Stack Developer built websites using Angular in frontend and, also built Hybrid mobile applications using Ionic Framework. Used PHP for backend APIs and MySQL as database. It was a small team, so I used to take requirements from the client and made FRS, Wireframes etc. for a quality delivery.

SKILLS

- Angular
- ionic Framework
- Typescript
- JavaScript
- HTML / CSS
- React JS
- Flutter
- Blockchain

EDUCATION

B.Sc.I.T.

2012-2015

Vidyalankar School of Information Technology (University of Mumbai)

HSC

2012

Guru Nanak College (MSBSHSE)

